Selected project for Guangdong Province Original Online Audio-Visual Premium Project Database.
مشروع مختار لمكتبة مشاريع غوانغدونغ الأصلية للمحتوى السمعي البصري عبر الإنترنت.
Does he make you drink a lot of water every time you come back?
هل في كل مرة تعود فيها،
and force you to drink a lot of water?
يجبرك على شرب كمية كبيرة من الماء؟
No wonder every time I go out,
لا عجب أنه في كل مرة أخرج،
he always gives me a
يعطيني دائمًا
blue little pill,
حبة زرقاء صغيرة،
saying it's Viagra,
يقول إنها فياغرا،
and makes me come back on time.
ويطلب مني العودة في الوقت المحدد.
I thought
كنت أظن
he was caring for me.
أنه يهتم بي.
This devil's spice.
هذا حار جدًا كالشيطان.
It's too devilish.
إنه شيطاني للغاية،
It's killing me with spice.
يكاد يقتلني من شدة الحرارة.
I'm all fired up now.
لقد أصبت بالتهاب.
Bro,
أخي،
I want to go exercise.
أريد أن أمارس بعض الرياضة.
(A leopard can't change its spots.)
(الكلب لا يغير عادته في أكل القذارة).
Bro, don't scold me.
أخي، لا تشتمني.
I know you care about me the most.
أعرف أنك تحبني كثيرًا.
(Come back in an hour.)
(عد خلال ساعة).
(I'll kill you if you're late.)
(إذا تأخرت سأقتلك).
Bro,
أخي،
can you give me some more of that medicine?
أين دواؤك؟ أعطني المزيد منه.
Your medicine is strong.
دواؤك قوي المفعول.
Thanks, bro.
شكرا يا أخي.
I'm off.
سأذهب الآن.
My brother is trying to poison me.
أخي يريد أن يسممني.
I can tell you
يمكنني أن أخبركم.
where they are.
أين هم؟
However,
ولكن.
the details of how we killed them
كيف قتلنا الناس بالتحديد.
will have to wait until we're all together.
دعونا ننتظر حتى نجتمع جميعا ثم نتحدث.
You go that way.
اذهب إلى هناك.
Run this way.
اركض إلى هنا.
Go!
هيا.
Stay alert.
كن حذرا.
Master.
يا معلم.
The person has escaped.
لقد هرب الرجل.
It's almost been 24 hours.
لقد مر ما يقرب من 24 ساعة الآن.
You don't have enough evidence.
ليس لديك أدلة كافية.
You'll have to release me soon.
يجب أن تطلق سراحي على الفور.
Where did he go?
أين ذهب بالضبط؟
Haven't I told you already?
ألم أخبرك بالفعل؟
Still pretending?
ما زلت تتظاهر؟
You said your brother told you to return on time.
قلت إن أخاك طلب منك العودة في الوقت المحدد.
Tell the truth quickly.
قل الحقيقة بسرعة.
Are you deliberately
هل تعمدت ذلك؟
delaying to let them escape?
تأخير الوقت للسماح لهم بالهروب؟
Where did he escape to?
إلى أين هرب؟
Wu Xianming.
وو شيان مينغ.
Did you know from the beginning
هل كنت تعرف منذ البداية
that you were taking poison?
أنك تناولت السم؟
You're his own brother.
أنت شقيقه.
He's trying to take your life,
إنه يريد قتلك.
his own brother's life.
حياة أخيه الشقيق.
Officer,
أيها الشرطي.
do you know
هل تعرف
what it means to be brothers?
ما معنى الأخ الشقيق؟
My life
حياتي
was given by my brother.
منحها لي أخي.
If he wants it,
إذا أراد
he can take it.
فليأخذها.
The test results are out.
لقد ظهرت نتائج الفحص.
The handwriting couldn't be confirmed,
لا يمكن التأكد من خط اليد.
but the sand does contain
لكن الرمل يحتوي بالفعل على
traces of chili powder.
كمية ضئيلة من مسحوق الفلفل الحار.
Lieutenant Xu.
الضابط شو.
For now, we can only confirm
في الوقت الحالي، يمكننا فقط التأكد
that what Wu Xianming said
مما قاله وو شيان مينغ
about the hiding place is correct.
أن مكان الاختباء صحيح.
I remember
أتذكر
when the two brothers were young,
أن الأخوين عندما كانا صغيرين
they didn't go to school.
لم يذهبا إلى المدرسة.
One was a mute at a slaughterhouse,
أحدهما أبكم يعمل في المسلخ
the other was an idle troublemaker.
والآخر متسكع عديم الفائدة.
There's one more person.
هناك شخص آخر.
He's been hiding behind the two brothers.
كان يختبئ خلف الأخوين طوال الوقت.
the one controlling everything.
الذي يتحكم في كل شيء.
The mastermind suspect.
المشتبه به وراء الكواليس.
Give me the money.
أعطني المال.
All of you, get out of the car.
انزلوا جميعا من السيارة.
If that's the case,
إذا كان الأمر كذلك،
this person is not to be underestimated.
فهذا الشخص ليس عاديا.
He can make the two brothers risk their lives for him.
يمكنه جعل الأخوين يخاطران بحياتهما من أجله.
They're already preparing to flee the city.
لقد استعدوا بالفعل للهروب من المدينة.
Notify the relevant departments.
أبلغ الإدارات المعنية.
Set up checkpoints
عند كل تقاطع طرق.
at every intersection.
ضع نقاط تفتيش.
Captain Xu,
الضابط شو.
let me give it a try.
دعني أحاول.
What?
ماذا؟
I'll interrogate him.
دعني أستجوبه.
Wu Xianming
وو شيان مينغ.
doesn't have much time left.
لن يعيش طويلا.
The drugs have already spread throughout his organs.
دخل الدواء بالفعل إلى جميع أعضاء الجسم.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
لماذا لم تخبرني بذلك من قبل؟
While you were on the mission,
أثناء قيامك بالمهمة،
Yao Jiajian and I
أنا وياو جيا جيان
conducted a thorough examination
قمنا بفحص عميق
of his physical condition.
لحالته الصحية.
He really doesn't have long to live.
إنه حقا لن يعيش طويلا.
I suspect
أشك
they've already planned their escape.
أنهم قد وضعوا خطة للهروب منذ فترة طويلة.
If we don't get
إذا لم نستطع
some information out of him now,
الحصول على بعض المعلومات من الاستجواب الآن،
it might be too late.
فقد يكون الأوان قد فات حقا.
Why does your brother like to eat ghost peppers?
لماذا يحب أخوك أكل الفلفل الحار جدا؟
What are you talking about?
ماذا تقول؟
I'm very curious.
أنا فضولي جدا.
This kind of pepper,
هذا النوع من الفلفل الحار
even half a piece
حتى نصف حبة منه
is too much for most people to handle.
يصعب على معظم الناس تحملها.
Does your brother have some kind of superpower?
هل لدى أخيك قدرات خارقة؟
I don't know.
لا أعرف.
I believe your own brother
أنا أثق بأن أخاك الحقيقي
wouldn't give you poison.
لن يعطيك سما لتأكله.
To avenge you,
من أجل الانتقام لك
stabbing someone three times,
طعن شخص ثلاث مرات
this is what a mute brother
هذا ما يمكن لأخ أبكم
can do for his younger brother.
أن يفعله لأخيه الأصغر.
What exactly are you trying to say?
ما الذي تريد قوله بالضبط؟
The drug
الدواء
was given to your brother by someone else.
أعطاه شخص آخر لأخيك.
Your brother knew the drug was poisoned,
أخوك يعرف أن الدواء مسموم
yet he still gave it to you.
ومع ذلك أعطاك إياه لتأكله.
Do you know why?
هل تعرف لماذا؟
Because in his eyes,
لأنه في نظره،
you're nothing but a burden.
أنت مجرد عبء.
From beginning to end,
منذ البداية حتى النهاية،
from childhood to adulthood,
منذ الصغر حتى الكبر،
you've always been a burden.
كنت دائمًا عبئًا.
You made him mute.
لقد تسببت في أن يصبح أخرس،
You got him thrown in detention.
وتسببت في سجنه،
Because of you, he now
وتسببت في أنه الآن
has to prematurely
مضطر للهروب
flee from police pursuit.
من مطاردة الشرطة قبل الأوان.
You're talking nonsense.
أنت تهذي.
You know it yourself,
أنت تعرف ذلك بنفسك،
you just don't dare to admit it.
لكنك لا تجرؤ على الاعتراف به.
I don't admit it.
لا أعترف بذلك.
You think you're considering their best interests
تظن أنك تفكر في مصلحتهم
by ending your life,
بالموت،
but in reality, your death
لكن في الواقع، موتك
is exactly the outcome they want.
هو النتيجة التي يريدونها.
Impossible.
مستحيل.
They never wanted to take you with them.
هم لا يريدون أخذك معهم على الإطلاق.
They just wanted to get rid of you.
هم فقط يريدون التخلص منك.
Impossible.
مستحيل.
My brother has already arranged for a fishing boat.
أخي حجز قارب الصيد بالفعل.
He wouldn't lie to me.
لا يمكن أن يخدعني.
Alright.
حسنا.
You're setting me up.
أنتم تحفرون حفرة.
You're deceiving me.
خدعتموني.
You're here so early.
جئت مبكرا جدا.
Come over here.
تعال هنا.
Hurry up.
أسرع.
Coming.
قادم.
Hurry, hurry.
أسرع، أسرع.
Come on, let's go.
هيا، هيا، هيا.
You're here early.
لماذا جئت مبكرا هكذا؟
Let's go.
هيا بنا.
I'll pay you when we get there.
سأعطيك المال عندما نصل.
Alright.
حسنا.
Police!
الشرطة!
Put the knife down.
ألق السكين.
Don't move!
لا تتحرك!
(Let me go.)
(دعني أذهب)
You have nowhere to run.
لا مفر لك.
Cut the crap.
كفى ثرثرة.
He needs medical treatment.
إنه بحاجة إلى العلاج.
Let him go.
أطلق سراحه.
I'll be your hostage.
سأكون رهينتك.
A cop's life is worth more than his.
حياة شرطي أثمن من حياته.
Come here.
تعال هنا.
Put your hands up.
ارفع يديك.
Get down.
انحنِ.
Calm down.
تمالك نفسك.
Take it easy.
هدئ من روعك.
Stay calm.
كن هادئًا.
Wu Zongfan.
وو زونغ فان.
What's your relationship with Wu Xianda and Wu Xianming?
ما علاقتك بـوو شيان دا ووو شيان مينغ
what's your relationship with them?
؟
I'm their distant cousin.
أنا ابن عمهم البعيد.
you know, the very distant kind.
من النوع البعيد جدًا.
You're quite decisive in admitting that.
اعترافك حاسم للغاية.
Well, we're relatives.
إنهم أقارب.
There's nothing to hide.
ليس هناك ما يخفى.
Alright.
حسنًا.
No hiding then.
لا تخفِ شيئًا.
Then tell me about your criminal activities.
إذن أخبرنا عن تفاصيل جريمتك.
As their older cousin,
أنا الأخ الأكبر
I failed to guide them properly.
الذي فشل في تربيتهم بشكل صحيح
I let them break the law.
مما جعلهم يرتكبون جرائم.
So according to you,
وفقًا لما تقول
these two murder cases
هاتان جريمتا القتل
have nothing to do with you?
لا علاقة لك بهما.
Of course they're related to me.
بالطبع لهما علاقة بي.
of course they're related to me.
بالتأكيد لهما علاقة بي.
The two of them robbed and killed people.
الأخوان سرقا المال وقتلا الناس
I didn't keep them in check.
لم أستطع السيطرة عليهما
Three lives were lost because of it.
مما أدى إلى مقتل ثلاثة أشخاص
I can't escape responsibility for that.
لا يمكنني التنصل من المسؤولية عن هذا.
You seem quite aware.
أنت واعٍ جدًا.
Officer,
أيها الضابط
where's my chili?
أين الفلفل الحار الخاص بي؟
Can I have some?
أعطني بعضًا منه.
What's the rush?
لماذا أنت مستعجل هكذا؟
We're not done talking yet.
لم ننتهِ من الحديث بعد.
Haven't we finished talking?
ألم ننتهِ من الحديث؟
I've already told you,
لقد أخبرتك بكل شيء.
the two brothers
الأخوان
were addicted to gambling and short on money.
مقامران ويحتاجان إلى المال
They heard
سمعوا
that Zhao Dachuan made a lot of money selling fish.
أن تشاو داتشوان كسب الكثير من المال من بيع الأسماك
So they argued
فبدأوا يتجادلون
about robbing him.
حول سرقة أمواله.
I tried my best to dissuade them,
حاولت إقناعهم بكل الطرق
but I couldn't stop them.
لكنني لم أتمكن من إيقافهم
They committed such a heinous act.
فارتكبوا هذا العمل الشنيع.
Later,
بعد ذلك
the two brothers came to me.
جاء الأخوان إليّ
At first,
في البداية
I didn't agree.
رفضت
They knelt down and begged me
لكنهما ركعا وتوسلا إليّ
to help them get a boat.
ليساعدهما في الحصول على قارب.
Being relatives,
بما أنهم أقارب
I softened
رق قلبي
and agreed.
ووافقت.
The forensic team examined your cleaver.
فحص الطب الشرعي سكين تقطيع العظام الخاصة بك
They found traces of
ووجدوا آثارًا متبقية
Zhu Shan's blood on it.
من دم تشو شان.
How do you explain that?
كيف تفسر ذلك؟
The cleaver belongs to the two brothers.
السكين تخص الأخوين
Their fingerprints should be on it, right?
يجب أن تكون بصمات أصابعهما عليها، أليس كذلك؟
Degree.
درجة المتجر.